<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Manchester United</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">GGMU!!!</string>
    <string name="article_text">Manchester United Football Club is a commercial football club based in Old Trafford Greater Manchester England that competes in the Premier League the top flight of English football Nicknamed the Red Devils the club was founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878,
        but changed its name to Manchester United in 1902. The club moved from Newton Heath to its current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910.
Manchester United have won the joint-record number of trophies in English club football,[5][6] including a record 20 League titles, 12 FA Cups, five League Cups and a record 21 FA Community Shields. They have won the European Cup/UEFA Champions League three times,
        and the UEFA Europa League, the UEFA Cup Winners Cup, the UEFA Super Cup, the Intercontinental Cup and the FIFA Club World Cup once each. In 1968 under the management of Matt Busby 10 years after eight of the clubs players were killed in the Munich air disaster they became the first English club to win the European Cup Alex Ferguson is the clubs
        longestserving and most successful manager winning 38 trophies including 13 league titles 5 FA Cups and 2 UEFA Champions League titles between 1986 and 2013 7 8 9 In the 1998 to 99 season under Ferguson the club became the first in the history of English football to achieve the European treble of the Premier League, FA Cup and UEFA Champions League.
        [10] In winning the UEFA Europa League under José Mourinho in 2016–17, the most recent trophy won by the club, they also became one of five clubs to have won the original three main UEFA club competitions the Champions League Europa League and Cup Winners Cup
        The team first entered the English First Division, then the highest league in English football, for the start of the 1892-93 season. Our club name changed to Manchester United Football Club in 1902, and we won the first of our 20 English League titles in 1908. In 1910, we moved to Old Trafford, our current stadium.
        /n

        The team played in the Football League for the very first time in 1892 (they should not be confused with Manchester Football Club, founded in 1860 and participated in the FA Cup in the 1870s before shifting to Rugby). But, they were relegated after two years. Next, a new group of local businessmen then took over the roles and responsibilities of the club and named it as Manchester United in 1902.
        The newly named club won the title of English League in 1908 under the guidance of Ernest Mangnall. The first FA Cup trophy was obtained the following year. The team then shifted to the current stadium, Old Trafford in 1910.

    </string>
</resources>